clikrev.com 2015-03-15

# clikrev. : innovation in online income

﻿ 

## Privacy Policy

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address and phone number. You may however visit our site anonymously.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  

  * To personalize your experience
  * To improve our website
  * To improve customer service
  * To process transactions ( Your purchases and withdrawals )
  * To send periodic emails ( Regarding our services )

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server.

Your password is saved in an irreversible format.

Transactions are only completed through processor accounts where the only information stored is your username or email (depending on the processor used).

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. 

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. Members and advertisers also display third party content and links as included with purchased services on our website.

These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on December 18, 2014

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. admin[at]clikrev.com
